{
  "quizInfo": {
    "Subject": "Practical Research 1",
    "Term": "First Quarter",
    "Title": "Module 3 - Lesson 1",
    "LastModified": "14 August 2025",
    "Authors": [
      "Alexander Oro"
    ],
    "References": [
      "Module 3 - Lesson 1.pdf"
    ]
  },
  "quizData": [
    {
      "question": "What is similar to making a house, car, or cake which needs appropriate materials and a necessary process?",
      "answer": "Designing research",
      "choices": [
        "Grounded Theory",
        "Case Study",
        "Ethnographic",
        "Designing research"
      ],
      "reference": "Designing a Research Topic",
      "term": "Module 3 Lesson 1"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is an example of a research topic that can be formulated based on issues encountered inside the classroom?",
      "answer": "“Parental involvement in student achievement”",
      "choices": [
        "“Parental involvement in student achievement”",
        "“Home environment on student learning”",
        "“Community outreach programs on youth behavior”",
        "“Parental discipline styles on child Behavior”"
      ],
      "reference": "Designing a Research Topic",
      "term": "Module 3 Lesson 1"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is an example of a research topic about learners' attitudes and hindrances?",
      "answer": "“Stress and time management among students”",
      "choices": [
        "“School cleanliness and student health”",
        "“Stress and time management among students”",
        "“Youth participation in community development”",
        "“Home environment on student learning”"
      ],
      "reference": "Designing a Research Topic",
      "term": "Module 3 Lesson 1"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is an example of a research topic based on observations of problems inside the classroom?",
      "answer": "“School cleanliness and student health”",
      "choices": [
        "“Parental discipline styles on child Behavior”",
        "“Community outreach programs on youth behavior”",
        "“School cleanliness and student health”",
        "“Stress and time management among students”"
      ],
      "reference": "Designing a Research Topic",
      "term": "Module 3 Lesson 1"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is an example of a research topic that might bother you on a daily basis at home?",
      "answer": "“Home environment on student learning”",
      "choices": [
        "“Home environment on student learning”",
        "“Parental involvement in student achievement”",
        "“School cleanliness and student health”",
        "“Community outreach programs on youth behavior”"
      ],
      "reference": "Designing a Research Topic",
      "term": "Module 3 Lesson 1"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is an example of a research topic that considers things that bother you at home?",
      "answer": "“Parental discipline styles on child Behavior”",
      "choices": [
        "“Stress and time management among students”",
        "“Parental discipline styles on child Behavior”",
        "“Youth participation in community development”",
        "“Parental involvement in student achievement”"
      ],
      "reference": "Designing a Research Topic",
      "term": "Module 3 Lesson 1"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is an example of a research topic that can come from the usual complaints of a neighbor regarding practices in the barangay?",
      "answer": "“Community outreach programs on youth behavior”",
      "choices": [
        "“Community outreach programs on youth behavior”",
        "“Home environment on student learning”",
        "“Parental involvement in student achievement”",
        "“School cleanliness and student health”"
      ],
      "reference": "Designing a Research Topic",
      "term": "Module 3 Lesson 1"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is an example of a research topic based on situations in the community that need to be improved?",
      "answer": "“Youth participation in community development”",
      "choices": [
        "“Parental discipline styles on child Behavior”",
        "“Stress and time management among students”",
        "“Youth participation in community development”",
        "“Home environment on student learning”"
      ],
      "reference": "Designing a Research Topic",
      "term": "Module 3 Lesson 1"
    },
    {
      "question": "What research design is appropriate for the topic “Parental involvement in student achievement”?",
      "answer": "Case Study",
      "choices": [
        "Phenomenological",
        "Grounded Theory",
        "Historical",
        "Case Study"
      ],
      "reference": "Designing a Research Topic",
      "term": "Module 3 Lesson 1"
    },
    {
      "question": "What research design can be used for the topic “Stress and time management among students”?",
      "answer": "Phenomenological",
      "choices": [
        "Ethnographic",
        "Phenomenological",
        "Historical",
        "Grounded Theory"
      ],
      "reference": "Designing a Research Topic",
      "term": "Module 3 Lesson 1"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is another research design that can be used for the topic “Stress and time management among students”?",
      "answer": "Case Study",
      "choices": [
        "Case Study",
        "Grounded Theory",
        "Ethnographic",
        "Historical"
      ],
      "reference": "Designing a Research Topic",
      "term": "Module 3 Lesson 1"
    },
    {
      "question": "What research design can be used for the topic “Youth participation in community development”?",
      "answer": "Phenomenological",
      "choices": [
        "Phenomenological",
        "Case Study",
        "Ethnographic",
        "Grounded Theory"
      ],
      "reference": "Designing a Research Topic",
      "term": "Module 3 Lesson 1"
    }
  ]
}